# MOHAMMAD YUSUF BASHARI

### LEAD WEB DEVELOPER



myubash@gmail.com

Bandung, West Java, Indonesia www.linkedin.com/in/myubash

### PROFILE

Innovative Lead Developer with 3 years of industry experience and extensive programming knowledge. Experienced handling all stages of development and following all software guidelines. Troubleshoots bugs, improves on existing software and tests products in real-life situations.

## SKILLS

- JavaScript
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- MongoDB
- AWS Integration
- Node.js
- Git
- React.js
- Postman

# EDUCATION

# TELECOMMUNICATIONS ENGINEERING

**Telkom University** 

2011 - 2018

- PR Officer of Nihon no Matsuri EO (2011 - 2013)
- Web QA Intern at Transcosmos Inc Yokohama
  (2014)

## EXPERIENCE

#### LEAD WEB DEVELOPER

PT Star Karlo Indonesia

2022 - Present

- Collected and analyzed client requirements and incorporating business goals into project proposals.
- Interfaced with front-end and back-end development teams to develop unified product, smoothing out coding conflicts before problems arose.

### **BACK-END WEB DEVELOPER**

PT Star Karlo Indonesia

2021 - 2022

- Implemented changes and integrated requested elements to streamline business operations.
- Developed technical solutions required to accommodate specific user-facing assets

### FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER

PT Star Karlo Indonesia

2020 - 2021

- Collaborated with stakeholders during development processes to confirm creative proposals and design best practices.
- Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- Teamed on user-centric design strategy in translation of UX and business requirements into coded solutions.